<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Header on Arcadius Docs</title><link>/menus/header/</link><description>Recent content in Header on Arcadius Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/menus/header/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>&lt;option/> and &lt;options/> tags</title><link>/menus/header/options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/menus/header/options/</guid><description>Any key/value pair is valid and will be stored in the document, for scripts or the system to use.
Options are declared inside &amp;lt;header&amp;gt; tag with the following syntax:
&amp;lt;option name=&amp;#34;option name&amp;#34; value=&amp;#34;option value&amp;#34; /&amp;gt; You can also omit the value
&amp;lt;option name=&amp;#34;option name&amp;#34;/&amp;gt; When you access an option with an omitted value (with document.getOption(name: string) for example) it will return an empty string. If several values for the same option are set in a page, the last valid one is used.</description></item><item><title>&lt;style/> tag</title><link>/menus/header/style/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/menus/header/style/</guid><description>The style tag is used for connecting SCSS stylesheets to the document. This tag can be declared as many times as needed to link multiple stylesheets.
You can either specify a filepath to an SCSS file using the src attribute, or write SCSS inside of the style element.
Attributes Attribute Value Description Example src stylesheet file path Specifies the file path of a stylesheet to use in the current document .</description></item><item><title>&lt;java-object> tag</title><link>/menus/header/java-object/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/menus/header/java-object/</guid><description>The &amp;lt;java-object/&amp;gt; element is used to link to a specific java (or Kotlin) class to load and invoke as the document is loaded. This element uses the class-name attribute to find a class.
When a class is found, the system will first try to find a public static void onDomInitialize(Document) method in the class, if found, it is invoked.
If not found, then the system will look for a public constructor with a single Document parameter.</description></item></channel></rss>